tvforadult.com 2016-05-17

# Privacy Policy

TVFORADULT respects your privacy. This policy explains how TVFORADULT will treat information that it may obtain from you as you make use of the TVFORADULT.com site. The owners and operators of TVFORADULT.com ("TVFORADULT") provide the TVFORADULT.com site, the TVFORADULT Blog, TVFORADULT Radio, and all services provided through them (the "Service") subject to the terms of this Privacy Policy. By using the Service, you accept and agree to this Privacy Policy.

The Privacy Policy may change from time to time, without notice other than appearing on the TVFORADULT website. Your continued use of the Service constitutes your agreement to all revisions to the TOS. This Privacy Policy was last revised on 10th of May 2011.

## The TVFORADULT Service and Third Party Sites

This Privacy Policy applies solely to the TVFORADULT Service. The Service may contain links to third party websites that are not owned or controlled by TVFORADULT. TVFORADULT has no control over, and assumes no responsibility for, the content, privacy policies, or practices of any third party website. You agree that you are responsible for reviewing and understanding the privacy policies (if any) of any third party websites you may access through this Service. By using this Service, you release TVFORADULT from any and all liability arising from your use of any third party website to which a link may be provided.

## Information Collected by this Service

When you use the Service, we may collect passive information about your visit. Passive information is any form of aggregate data, navigational data, tracking data, click-stream data, or historical data. It may include the domain name of your internet service provider (e.g., whether you logged on from aol.com or whitehouse.gov), referral data (e.g., the address of the last URL you visited prior to clicking through to the TVFORADULT website) and browser and platform type (e.g., a Firefox browser on a Macintosh platform). We use this information to track how users are accessing and using the Service.

In addition, when you use the Service we generally collect the IP Address of the computer you are using to access it. (An IP, or "Internet Protocol," address is a unique number associated with your computer, that may be communicated to other computers and servers when you use the Internet.) We use this information for purposes of security and anti-fraud protection.

TVFORADULT also uses cookies and/or web beacons. (A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from a Web server and stored on your computer's hard drive, and that may be accessed when you use a website or other online service. A web beacon is a small, transparent graphic image placed on a website, which allows the site to record the actions of a visitor opening the page that contains the beacon.)

We may use cookies or web beacons to: (1) determine whether users of the Service are unique, or whether the same user is using the Service on multiple occasions; (2) help deliver advertisements; (3) track usage throughout various components of the TVFORADULT website and the Service (e.g., tracking where traffic comes from, how traffic flows within the Service, etc.); (4) store your agreement to the terms and conditions for entering and using the Service; (5) monitor aggregate metrics such as total number of visitors, pages viewed, etc.

These kinds of information do not, on their own, personally identify you. However, they can potentially be combined with information obtained from other sources in order to identify you. TVFORADULT does not ordinarily seek or obtain personally identifying information about users from others. It does reserve the right to seek such information in the event of a violation of the TVFORADULT [Terms of Service](http://www.tvforadult.com/sex/component/content/?id=122&Itemid=1027), in the event of a dispute between TVFORADULT and you, or if required by law to do so.

## Content You Submit TVFORADULT to or Communicate Using the Service

TVFORADULT may allow you to submit and communicate audio and video content, text, links, and other content ("User Content"). Except with respect to User Content that you are expressly allowed and enabled to keep private using the TVFORADULT Community uploading function, User Content that you submit to TVFORADULT or communicate using the Service, including any personal information included in your User Content, becomes publicly available and can be seen, collected, and used by others. Once made public User Content cannot be made private again. In addition, User Content you communicate using the Service may be recorded, stored, copied and/or retransmitted by TVFORADULT, including but not limited to audio or video content submitted to the TVFORADULT Community, TVFORADULT Blog and calls made to TVFORADULT Radio. You should not submit or communicate any content using the Service that you do not want to be seen, collected, or used by others.

In the process of posting User Content, you may be asked to provide some personally identifying information, such as your name, address, e-mail address, a password, and other documentation. You may also be asked to provide such information in order to use certain features of the Service, including but not limited certain features of the TVFORADULT blog available only to registered users.

We will keep a record of the information you provide, including your personally identifiable information. That information may be linked in our records to other information you provide, including User Content. We will not publically post your name or other personally identifying information, and we will not provide such information to our advertisers or business partners without your permission. However, some of the information you provide in registering for and using the TVFORADULT Community feature will be displayed to other members of the TVFORADULT Community, and may become public. In addition, we may disclose the personally identifying information and documentation you provide in some limited circumstances, as set forth below ("Permitted Disclosures of Personal Information").

## Use of Visitor Information Collected by the Service

We do not share personally identifiable information about users of the Service in the ordinary operation of the Service, unless you have included such information in User Content that you submit or communicate using the Service, such as through the TVFORADULT Community feature. We may obtain and merge information about users and usage of the Service into aggregated data, which may then be used by us and/or shared with advertisers or others. When we provide aggregated information to outside companies, they will not be able to identify you or contact you based on that data.

## Usage Information - Collection and Use by Advertisers and Others

TVFORADULT allows other companies to display advertisements using the Service. These companies use technology to deliver advertisements you see using the Service directly to your browser. In doing so, they may automatically receive your IP address. Other companies that place advertising using the Service may have the ability to use cookies and/or web beacons to collect information, including information about your usage of the Service. We do not control the processes that advertisers use to collect information. However, IP addresses, cookies and web beacons alone generally cannot be used to identify individuals, only machines. Therefore, advertisers and others whose advertisements or content may be provided through the Service generally will not know who you are unless you provide additional information to them, by responding to an advertisement, by entering into an agreement with them, or by some other means.

## Children's Privacy

We do not knowingly allow children to use the Service, and all users of the Service must confirm that they are at least 21 years old. We do not collect or maintain information from those we actually know are under 21, and no part of our Service is designed to attract anyone under 21. If we become aware that anyone under the age of 21 is using the Service, their access to the Service will be terminated.

## Permitted Disclosures of Personal Information

TVFORADULT generally does not collect personally identifiable information (data such as your name, email address, password, and the content of your communications) unless you submit or communicate User Content through the Service, or register with us in order to use certain features of the Service. TVFORADULT will not disclose any personally identifiable information it collects or obtains except: (1) as described in the TVFORADULT [Terms of Service](http://www.tvforadult.com/sex/component/content/?id=122&Itemid=1027) or this Privacy Policy; (2) after obtaining your permission to a specific use or disclosure; (3) if TVFORADULT is required to do so in order to comply with any valid legal process or governmental request (such as a court order, search warrant, subpoena, civil discovery request, or statutory requirement); (4) as required to protect TVFORADULT's property, safety, or operations, or the property or safety of others; or (5) to a business that acquires TVFORADULT, or the assets of TVFORADULT in connection with which such information has been collected or used; or (6) as otherwise required by law.

## Security

Some components of the Service may use security measures to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of information that is transmitted through the Service. However, no data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personally identifiable information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit, and you do so at your own risk.

## Questions or Concerns

If you have any questions, concerns or complaints about TVFORADULT's Privacy Policy and use of personal information, please contact us using our email: [[info@tvforadult.com](mailto:info@tvforadult.com)](http://www.redtube.com/contact).

Questa normativa sulla privacy ("informativa") è applicata a tutti i siti operati da TVFORADULT.COM e alle sue sussidiarie (i "siti di TVFORADULT", i "nostri siti").  
TVFORADULT.COM ("TVFORADULT", "noi") comprende l'importanza della privacy dei suoi utenti, abbonati e visitatori ("utenti", "voi") e ha sviluppato questa normativa per assicurare che la privacy dei suoi utenti sia protetta durante l'utilizzo di uno qualsiasi dei siti appartenenti a questa rete.

1\. Un messaggio perticolare sui bambini.   
È vietato alle persone minori di diciotto anni usare qualsiasi dei nostri siti o servizi, pertanto chiediamo ai minori di non inviarci informazioni di alcun tipo.

2\. A proposito delle informazioni raccolte da TVFORADULT.   
Durante il processo di registrazione per qualsiasi sito della rete di TVFORADULT, potresti inserire certe informazioni d'identificazione personale, incluse ma non limitate a: nome, indirizzo, email, carta di credito e informazioni bancarie.

I siti di TVFORADULT usano "cookie" per salvare e alle volte rintracciare alcune informazioni, per rendere la tua esperienza online più facile e personalizzata. I cookie sono piccoli segmenti di dati salvati sul disco fisso da parte del browser dell'utente. I cookie possono registrare le informazioni di una pagina web visitata dall'utente per poi semplificare le future interazioni con quel sito da quello stesso utente oppure per semplificare le transazioni su pagine simili. I cookie rendono più semplice navigare da pagina web a pagina web e completare transazioni in Internet.

La maggior parte dei browser sono inizialmente impostati ad accettare i cookie ma si possono modificare le preferenze per essere avvisati quando un cookie sta per essere scaricato oppure vietare l'abilità di scaricare i cookie sul tuo computer da questi siti. Se scegli di bloccare tutti i cookie, alcune parti dei siti di TVFORADULT potrebbero non funzionare correttamente. Per maggiori informazioni sui cookie, puoi visitare la pagina: <http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/HTTP_cookie>.

Potremmo inoltre usare tecnologia Internet standard, come gli identificatori web o "gif" 1x1 e altre tecnologie simili (chiamate nel collettivo "Pixel tags"), per controllare il tuo utilizzo dei nostri siti. Un 'Pixel tag' è un'immagine elettronica, solitamente formata da un singolo pixel (1x1), che non è visibile ai visitatori del sito e che potrebbe essere associata a dei cookie sul loro disco fisso. Potremmo anche includere dei 'Pixel tags' in avvisi pubblicitari o promozionali o altri messaggi email per determinare se i messaggi sono stati aperti o se c'è stata qualche altra azione. Queste informazioni ci permettono di personalizzare i servizi che offriamo.

Se ci invii della corrispondenza, come email o lettere, o se altri utenti o persone appartenenti ad altri siti TVFORADULT o esterne ad essi, ci inviano della corrispondenza sulle tue attività o annunci in qualsiasi dei siti di TVFORADULT, potremmo salvare queste informazioni che saranno comunque trattate solamente dal personale o dai rappresentanti autorizzati di TVFORADULT. Potremmo inoltre salvare i commenti fatti su di te da altri utenti.

In alcuni dei nostri siti, potresti usare il nostro servizio di raccomandazione per fa sapere di noi a un amico o amici. In questo caso, ti chiederemo il nome e l'indirizzo email dell'amico (o amici) e gli invieremo un singolo invito a visitare il nostro sito. Salviamo queste informazioni per il solo scopo di inviare questa singola email e controllare lo stato della raccomandazione. Il tuo amico (o amici) può contattarci all'indirizzo [info@tvforadult.com](mailto:info@tvforadult.com) per richiedere di rimuovere l'indirizzo email dai nostri archivi.

3\. Il nostro utilizzo delle tue informazioni d'identificazione personale.   
Usiamo le tue informazioni d'identificazione personale all'interno dell'azienda per migliorare i nostri sforzi di marketing, analizzare l'utilizzo dei siti di TVFORADULT, migliorare il nostro contenuto e le nostre offerte e personalizzare il contenuto e l'apparenza dei nostri siti. Crediamo che questi utilizzi ci permettano di migliorare i nostri siti per personalizzarli alla tua esperienza online.

Potremmo inoltre usare le tue informazioni d'identificazione personale per inviare delle informazioni che in alcuni casi potrebbero interessarti, come banner e promozioni.

Inviamo anche degli aggiornamenti periodici via email.

Potremmo usare le informazioni di carattere personale per risolvere dispute, correggere errori e rispettare qualsiasi accordo, politica e regolamento che governa l'utilizzo dei siti di TVFORADULT.

4\. La divulgazione dei tuo dati personali.   
NON vendiamo o affittiamo le tue informazioni personali d'identificazione a terzi per pubblicità o marketing senza il tuo permesso. Tuttavia, queste informazioni sono disponibili ai nostri fornitori di servizi (es. aziende di elaborazione creditizia o per servizi di pagamento) quando ritenuto necessario o appropriato per lo svolgimento della loro attività nei siti di TVFORADULT.

Condividiamo le informazioni aggregate ad aziende pubblicitarie e a scopo promozionale. Tuttavia, in questi casi NON rilasciamo informazioni che potrebbero essere usate per identificarti. Alcune informazioni, come la tua password del sito TVFORADULT, il numero della tua carta di credito e il numero del tuo conto corrente non sono mai rilasciate.

Potremmo essere costretti a rilasciare le tue informazioni a enti governativi o a terzi, come nel caso di un ordine giudiziario, di comparizione o un mandato di perquisizione. Ci riserviamo il diritto di rilasciare le tue informazioni personali se siamo convinti che sia necessario per proteggere i nostri diritti o per far rispettare i nostri accordi, procedure e regole che governano il tuo utilizzo dei siti di TVFORADULT o per cooperare volontariamente con le forze dell'ordine.

Potremmo inoltre condividere o trasferire, alcune o tutte le tue informazioni personali tra le altre aziende della nostra rete o ad altri enti che non fanno parte della rete se questi acquistano, anche solo in parte, il servizio che contiene o utilizza le tue informazioni.

5\. Il tuo utilizzo dei dati personali degli utenti dei siti di TVFORADULT.   
È vietato l'uso delle informazioni degli altri utenti della rete di TVFORADULT, che siano private o meno, per scopi commerciali e pubblicitari o per molestie e minacce. Ci riserviamo il diritto di interdire chi non rispetta la privacy delle informazioni degli altri utenti o che viola qualsiasi accordo, procedura o regolamento che governa l'uso dei siti di TVFORADULT.

6\. Non divulgare i tuoi dati personali o la tua password.   
NON inviare, condividere o divulgare in luoghi pubblici - come forum, stanze chat o blog - qualsiasi tua informazione d'identificazione personale che non vuoi rendere nota ad altri utenti. Consigliamo di fare delle domande prima di condividere le proprie informazioni personali. Allo stesso modo, non dovresti mai condividere la tua password con altri. Se la tua password è compromessa, le tue informazioni personali potrebbero essere divulgate e potresti essere soggetto ad azioni legali per conto di terzi. Se per qualsiasi motivo la tua password è stata compromessa, dovresti immediatamente cambiarla o contattarci via email a [info@tvforadult.com](mailto:info@tvforadult.com).

7\. Come aggiornare, cambiare o rimuovere i tuoi dati personali.   
Una volta completata la registrazione, avrai la possibilità di rivedere e aggiornare la maggior parte delle tue informazioni d'identificazione personale, incluse, ma non limitate a:

Il tuo indirizzo email   
La tua città, provincia (o stato), CAP (o ZIP code) e nazione   
La tua password   
Il tuo profilo   
Accedi al tuo account e aggiorna le tue informazioni prontamente, seguendo le istruzioni che appariranno sullo schermo. Consigliamo vivamente di cambiare la password periodicamente per ridurre il rischio di accesso non autorizzato alle informazioni del tuo conto.

Se ci viene richiesto, rimuoveremo il numero di carta di credito e la data di scadenza dal nostro database. Per effettuare questa richiesta, inviaci un'email all'indirizzo [info@tvforadult.com](mailto:info@tvforadult.com). Ciò nonostante, manterremo nei nostri archivi alcune informazioni sulla carta di credito che useremo nel caso sia necessario risolvere dispute, correggere errori, rispettare gli accordi con banche e associazioni creditizie, migliorare la sicurezza, ridurre la possibilità di frode, conformarsi alle leggi federali e statali o per far rispettare accordi, procedure e regolamenti sull'utilizzo dei siti TVFORADULT. Le informazioni rimosse potrebbero rimanere in copie di backup o nelle cache di altri utenti. Ad esempio, le informazioni scambiate tra utenti potrebbero rimanere nella loro casella di posta, cache o archivio dei messaggi istantanei. Non siamo responsabili di tue informazioni salvate da altri utenti. Tutte le informazioni salvate da TVFORADULT o da enti sotto il suo controllo non sono rese disponibili a terzi eccetto quanto definito in questo regolamento.

8\. Raccolta di dati da parte di terzi.   
Questa normativa governa solamente l'utilizzo e la divulgazione di informazioni che raccogliamo da te. Le informazioni da te condivise con altri mentre utilizzi i nostri o altri siti in Internet, possono essere soggette a diverse normative per il loro utilizzo, manutenzione o divulgazione. TVFORADULT non gestisce le normative sulla privacy di altri enti e dove applicabile, sei soggetto alle normative di quelle parti.

Potremmo usare aziende esterne per inviare pubblicità per nostro conto. Queste aziende potrebbero usare cookie o Pixel tags per misurare l'efficacia della pubblicità.

9\. La sicurezza.   
I siti di TVFORADULT adottano misure di sicurezza ragionevoli per aiutare a proteggere ed evitare la perdita, l'uso improprio e l'alterazione delle informazioni in nostro possesso. Adottiamo le misure prevalenti in questo settore, come ad esempio firewall, per salvaguardare le informazioni d'identificazione personale. Sebbene la sicurezza "perfetta" non esiste, il nostro personale tecnico lavora duro per assicurare l'utilizzo sicuro dei nostri servizi.

10\. Ubicazione geografica.   
I siti di TVFORADULT sono situati negli Stati Uniti. Se stai visitando i nostri siti da un altro paese, i tuoi dati potrebbero essere trasferiti, salvati ed elaborati negli Stati Uniti. La protezione dei dati e alcune leggi degli Stati Uniti e di altre nazioni potrebbero non essere esaurienti come quelle del tuo paese.

11\. Aggiorna/Elimina/Opt-Out.   
Queste sono le alternative per modificare o cancellare le tue informazioni d'identificazione personale dal nostro database:

* Puoi inviare un'email all'indirizzo: [info@tvforadult.com](mailto:info@tvforadult.com);  
* Puoi accedere al sito e modificare o eliminare il tuo profilo;  
* Puoi inviare la tua richiesta per posta a: ;  
* Puoi chiamarci al numero: .

Usando le informazioni di contatto sopracitate, potresti anche ricevere email da pubblicitari esterni.

12\. Le revisioni alla normativa sulla privacy.   
I siti di TVFORADULT si riservano il diritto e a loro completa discrezione di rivedere, aggiungere, modificare o revocare questa normativa sulla privacy in qualsiasi momento e in qualsiasi modo nel rispetto dalla legge. I cambiamenti a questa normativa saranno resi validi tramite la pubblicazione di queste revisioni nei siti di TVFORADULT.  
NORMATIVA SULLA PRIVACY DI TVFORADULT.COM . In vigore dal: 06/01/2014
